

Mohamad Ikhwan Bin Johar

CGPA: 3.16

"Hi, my name is Mohamad Ikhwan Bin Johar and I'm a graduate from Universiti Teknologi MARA (UiTM) studying in Information Technology. I am interested in pursuing work in the IT industry / field . I have developed a few skill such as programming and other related to IT by participating in an internship in IT Consultation in my Diploma as trainee technician, and developing a library management system in my diploma final year project and also developing mobile application related to recycling in my degree final year project). I hope to become someone that become more well verse in IT industry by gaining experience through working

ikhwanj95@gmail.com

🤊 no.25 jln pi 9/6, taman pulai indah, Skudai, Malaysia

github.com/Sicx6

011-41312421

n linkedin.com/in/mohamad-ikhwan-935889214

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (HONS.)

Universiti Teknologi MARA (UiTM)

2018 - 2022

Courses

 Developing a Recycling related mobile application in Final Year Project

DIPLOMA IN SCIENCE COMPUTER

Kolej Universiti Poly-Tech MARA Kuala Lumpur(KUPTM)

2013 - 2016 CGPA: 2.84

Courses

 Creating a Library Mangement System using Visual Basic in Final Year Project

WORK EXPERIENCE

Protegee - Admin Asistant

Sime Darby Motors.

09/2022 - 1/2023 Ara Damansara

Achievements/Tasks

 Involve in sales operation related in aftersales and handling document and invoice related fleet and orders. Handling admin task such as filing, typing, copying, binding, scanning involving microsoft office and outlook.

IT Intern

Netherlands Maritime University College (NMUC)

10/2021 - 02/2022 Education Institution Johor Bahru, Johor

Achievements/Tasks

 Provide IT Support and services in hardware such as server, cctv, printer and software such as university website and management system. Also involve in documentation regarding IT in general.

Assistant Manager

7-Eleven Malaysia

11/2017 - 01/2018 Skudai

Achievements/Tasks

• Involve mainly in management, admin and sales.

Trainee Technician Portal One Sdn Bhd

10/2015 - 05/2016 IT Consultation Company Petaling Jaya

Achievements/Tasks

 Involve in computer maintenance service and other IT related equipment

SKILLS

Mobile Programming

Graphic Design

Mobile Application Development

Hardware Maintainence

Mobile Network

Technical Skills

Database

Network

Microsoft Office

People management

Leadership

Problem Solving

Critical Observation

CURRICULUM ACTIVITIES

Music Commercial Club (2018)

• Learn regarding music and how to improve leadership and teamwork

Pertandingan Kawad Kaki Antara Kompeni (11/2018)

• Third Place for the best uniform between the Kompeni

CERTIFICATES

Dart Certification Course - (07/2022)

Online learning about the dart programming language by Programming Hub

Easy Writing With Microsoft Word (01/2021)

Training on Microsoft product specifically in microsoft word

Usability Testing : SUS Tool (03/2021)

Managed to complete a System Usabiltity testing workshop.

Hybrid Mobile Application Using Flutter (03/2021)

Managed to complete a programming workshop on flutter topics.

Huawei HCIA Datacom - Attended (02/2022 - 03/2022)

Training about networking specifically in routing, switching, VLAN, WLAN and other related to networking.

The Complete 2021 Flutter Development Bootcamp with Dart (06/2022)

Online Bootcamp on flutter framework framework with dart as language for cross apps platform development.

Muet (2016)

Band 4

REFERENCECS

Madam Norisan Abd Karim

UiTM Academic Advisor - 03-55211207

Dr Jasber Kaur a/p Gian Singh

UiTM Final Year Project Supervisor - 03-55211207

WORK EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer

Dik Print

3/2017 - 05/2017

Multimedia/Printing Company

Design the banner, bunting, logo, t-shirt/shirt, sticker and others. Involve in printing product using heat press method for t-shirt.

LANGUAGES

English

Skudai

Full Professional Proficiency

Bahasa Malaysia

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

PROJECTS

Degree Final Year Project

Re-Cycle Apps

Present, develop, maintain, support and configure application for encouraging and helping the Household for helping to sort out and sending their recycling waste to the recycling waste in their area.

Personal Projects

To Do Apps

To Doey Apps allow user to create, tick if the task is finish and deleted them by long pressing the apps. Apps was built using flutter framework for practicing and as exercise to improve on flutter.

MyNews Apps

Develop to create news apps that simple and minimalist. The apps was built using flutter and also use rest api to pull the data and information regarding the news.

Shopping Apps

The apps was built using flutter framework for frontend, NodeJs for the backend and MongoDB and cloudinary for database and media storage. The apps mainly build for Ecommerce purpose. The apps using provider for state management and apps contain admin panel for admin to upload monitor the product available related. User can edit profile, add to cart item, buy item and other